techgeek365.com 2015-02-26

# Privacy Policy - TechGeek365

#### TechGeek365 Privacy Policy

TechGeek365 will not share your information with 3rd parties for any reason, **Ever**.

TechGeek365 respects your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us on our website. To that end, unless you designate otherwise or we state otherwise in this policy or at the time information is collected, any personal information you provide to TechGeek365 will be known only to two parties: you and TechGeek365. The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our site and its features. Personal information includes your full name, street and e-mail addresses, billing information, click-through activity and any other personal information you may provide here. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

##### **Traffic Data:**

Each time a visitor comes to the TechGeek365 website, our servers — like most on the web — collect some basic technical information, including, for example, the visitor’s domain name, referral data and browser and platform type.

We also count, track and aggregate the visitor’s activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our sites. To these ends, we may merge information about visitors and visits into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with our advertisers; but we will not disclose your individual identity or personally identifiable data without your permission. When we do present aggregated information to outside companies, no one will be able to identify you or contact you.

##### **Use Of Cookies:**

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies in a limited way to help deliver advertisements, to identify unique browsers that visit us and to track usage throughout our site.

The information about readership and site usage that TechGeek365 collects through cookies is aggregated into general reports about readership and not tied to individual identities.

Other companies which place advertising on our site also have the ability to assign their cookies to you in a process that TechGeek365 does not control. However, cookies cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines, so these advertisers will not know who you are.

##### **Promotions:**

From time to time, TechGeek365 may sponsor sweepstakes, contests or other events which require the collection, processing and storage of individual contact and demographic information to be used for the event. TechGeek365 may also co-sponsor these events along with other companies, in which case the user’s individual contact and demographic information is likely to be shared with other participating sponsors, who may use this information as they wish. A registrant’s personal contact and demographic information will not be released to any third-party organization other than named sponsors without the user’s consent, and TechGeek365 will request that such named sponsors uphold the privacy of the registrants’ information by not distributing or sharing such information with any other businesses or organizations.

##### **Surveys:**

TechGeek365 will from time to time conduct voluntary surveys of visitors to the site to obtain aggregate demographic information about them. Such information may be compiled and shared in the aggregate with advertisers and other third parties, but no personal details will be traceable or associated with specific individuals.

##### **Children’s Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is important to us. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

##### **Disclosure Of Personal Information:**

TechGeek365 will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except (i) as described in this privacy policy, or (ii) as required by law to be disclosed. This policy does not protect information you post to any online bulletin board, chat room, newsgroup or other public forum within our website.

##### **Data Removal Policies:**

If you would like to remove your name and e-mail address from our registration database, you can send an e-mail requesting removal to:  **[contact@techgeek365.com](mailto:contact@techgeek365.com "Contact Us")**

##### **Other Websites:**

TechGeek365 contains many links to other sites on the web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites.

##### **Who Can I Ask Questions To?**

If you have any further questions or concerns about our privacy policies and use of personal information, please send an to: [ **contact@techgeek365.com**](mailto:contact@techgeek365.com "Contact Us")
